Guide to the Colgate University Core Curriculum records A1100
Special Collections and University Archives, Colgate University Libraries
Colgate University Core Curriculum records
1929-1989
A1100
Special Collections and University Archives, Colgate University Libraries
7 Cubic feet
Colgate University.
Access to Collection
Collection is open for research; however, special restrictions may apply to portions of this collection in accordance with the Colgate University Archives policy on restricted records. These restrictions may include, but are not limited to, University administrative records (closed for 30 years from date of creation), employee records (closed for 75 years), and student records (closed for 75 years in accordance with the Federal Family Education and Privacy Rights Acts (FERPA)). During the restricted period, the records will be made available to the office of origin, the staff of the University Archives, and officers of the University as necessary. Please contact Special Collections and University Archives for further information.
Related Materials in this Repository
See also A1105 Colgate University Division of University Studies records.
Colgate University--Curricula.; Annual reports.; Syllabi.; Textbooks.; Universities and colleges--Curricula.
- Readings in Philosophy, Religion and Drama, Core 170-180, 1969 Fall (Box 1, Folder 1)
- A Survey in Social Science Part I, 1937-1938 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- A Survey in Social Science Vol. V, 1939-1940 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- A Survey in Social Science Vol. VI, 1939-1940 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Western Civilization Study Guide Vol. I, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Western Civilization Study Guide Vol. II, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Western Civilization Instructor's Manual, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Western Civilization Test Bank, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Problems in Physical Science, Instructor Manual, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- A Survey in Social Science Vol. II, 1939-1940 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- A Survey in Social Science Vol. III, 1939-1940 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Social Science Survey Course, 1930-1931 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Survey Course 3- The Social Sciences, 1929-1930 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Survey Course in the Social Sciences, 1933 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Problems in Physical Science, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Problems in Natural Science Part I, 1947 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Problems in Natural Science Part I, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Core 10 Manual- Problems in Natural Sciences, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Core 1 Manual- Problems in Physical Science, 1950 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Core 1 Notes- Problems in Physical Science, 1948 (Box 2, Folder 20)
- Survey in Physical Science Part 2, 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 21)
- Core 11 Manual, Problems in Physical Sciences, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 22)
- Core 10 Manual, Problems in Natural Science Vol. 1, 1965-1966 (Box 2, Folder 23)
- Music and the Visual Arts- Core 21 Syllabus, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 24)
- Colgate University Functional Writing Program, 1950-1951 (Box 2, Folder 25)
- Colgate University Functional Writing Program, 1953-1954 (Box 2, Folder 26)
- Core 23, 1959-1960 (Box 2, Folder 27)
- Writing Laboratory: Functional writing Assignments, etc., undated (Box 2, Folder 28)
- Core 23, Annual Reports, undated (Box 2, Folder 29)
- Core 23, Historical., undated (Box 2, Folder 30)
- Functional Writing Program, Sample Student Papers, undated (Box 3, Folder 31)
- Functional Writing Program: General., undated (Box 3, Folder 32)
- Functional Writing Assignments: Humanities, undated (Box 3, Folder 33)
- Functional Writing Assignments: Science, undated (Box 3, Folder 34)
- Functional Writing Assignments: Social Sciences, undated (Box 3, Folder 35)
- The Sciences at Colgate University, undated (Box 3, Folder 36)
- The Organism and the World of Life, 1936 (Box 3, Folder 37)
- Survey of Physical Sciences, 1934 (Box 3, Folder 38)
- Survey of Physical Sciences, 1935 (Box 3, Folder 39)
- Survey of Physical Sciences, 1936 (Box 3, Folder 40)
- Survey of Physical Sciences, 1937 (Box 3, Folder 41)
- E.G. Bewkes Et al. A Survey in Philosophy and Religion: Experience, Reason and Faith (USA: Harper, 1940). (Box 3, Folder 42)
- Colgate Readings in Philosophy and Religion, Core Course 5-6, 1949-1950 (Box 3, Folder 43)
- Colgate Readings in Philosophy and Religion Part II, Core Course 6, 1949 Spring (Box 3, Folder 44)
- Colgate Readings in Philosophy and Religion Part I, Core Course 5, 1948 Fall (Box 3, Folder 45)
- Readings in Philosophy, Religion and Drama, Core 17-18, 1966-1967 (Box 3, Folder 46)
- Basic Beliefs of Modern Culture, Core 13-14, 1956 Fall (Box 3, Folder 47)
- Basic Beliefs of Modern Culture Vol. 1, Core Course 5-6, 1954-1955 (Box 3, Folder 48)
- Basic Beliefs of Modern Culture Vol. 2, Core Course 5-6, 1954-1955 (Box 3, Folder 49)
- Basic Beliefs of Modern Culture Vol. 2, Core Course 5-6, 1953-1954 (Box 4, Folder 50)
- America in the World Community, Core 41, 1960-1961 (Box 4, Folder 51)
- Area Studies: World Wide Issues, Core 7-8, 1948 Spring (Box 4, Folder 52)
- Core 7.4- Koenig German, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 53)
- Core 31:75- The Andes Trilogy (Chile, Peru and Bolivia), 1963 Fall (Box 4, Folder 54)
- Area Studies 310- Latin America, 1949-1950 (Box 4, Folder 55)
- The Economy of Latin America, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 56)
- Core 7.6 and 8.6- Mediterranean Area, 1950-1951 (Box 4, Folder 57)
- Core 7.3- French Area Studies, 1947 (Box 4, Folder 58)
- Core 7.1 and 8.1- Britain and the Commonwealth of Nations, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 59)
- Core 7.1 and 8.1- Britain and the Commonwealth of Nations, 1947-1948 (Box 4, Folder 60)
- Colgate University Conference on Undergraduate Studies, 1956 April (Box 4, Folder 61)
- Core 32-33- American Ideals and Institutions Vol. 1, 1956-1957 (Box 5, Folder 62)
- Core 32-33- American Ideals and Institutions Vol. 2, 1956-1957 (Box 5, Folder 63)
- Problems of Contemporary Society, 1976 Fall (Box 5, Folder 64)
- Core 370- Values and Institutions, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 65)
- Core 370- Values and Institutions, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 66)
- Core 370- Values and Institutions, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 1969, Folder 67)
- Core 33-34- American Ideals and Institutions I, 1962-1963 (Box 5, Folder 68)
- Core 33-34- American Ideals and Institutions II, 1961-1962 (Box 5, Folder 69)
- Area IV- Values in a Changing World, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 70)
- Area 303- Problems of World Order, 1947-1948 (Box 5, Folder 71)
- Core 125- The Directivness of Organic Activities, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 72)
- Core 386A: Brazil, 1971 Fall (Box 6, Folder 73)
- Core 385: Caribbean Studies, 1976 Spring (Box 6, Folder 74)
- University Studies 231: Computers and Society, 1974 Fall (Box 6, Folder 75)
- Core 384: Kenya, 1971-1972 (Box 6, Folder 76)
- Core 382B: India, 1971 Spring (Box 6, Folder 77)
- Core 38:51: India Vol. 1, 1967 Fall (Box 6, Folder 78)
- Core 38:51: India Vol. 2, 1967 Fall (Box 6, Folder 79)
- Exploring the Social Order Vol. 3, 1938-1939 (Box 6, Folder 80)
- Information for the Visiting Committee for University Studies, 1960 (Box 6, Folder 81)
- BASH- Core 3 and 4, 1950 (Box 6, Folder 82)
- Core 3 and 4- Problems in Public Affairs, 1952 (Box 6, Folder 83)
- Exploring the Social Order Vol. 5, 1938-1939 (Box 7, Folder 84)
- Exploring the Social Order Vol. 6, 1938-1939 (Box 7, Folder 85)
- A Survey in Social Science Vol. 1, 1939-1940 (Box 7, Folder 87, Folder 86)
- Exploring the Social Order Vol. 4, 1938-1939 (Box 7, Folder 87)
- A Survey Course in Philosophy and Religion, undated (Box 7, Folder 88)
- A Survey in Social Science Part 2, 1937-1938 (Box 7, Folder 89)
- Exploring the Social Order Vol. 2, 1938-1939 (Box 7, Folder 90)